Leeroy Phili

Full Stack Web Developer

Address: 199 Richmond St W,

Toronto ON M5V 0H5

Phone: 416 828 4176 LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/leeroy-phili-0b0b5119b

Email: leeroyphili@gmail.com Portfolio: https://react-portfolio-leeroy.herokuapp.com/

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with a wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable backend and frontend development requirements.. Skillful creating servers and databases for functionality and designing and developing API's, Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 2 years of related experience

Technical Skills

Software Skills:

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js, MySQL, Mongo, Express.js, React, React Native, Redux, SASS

Work History

2020-11 - Current

Full Stack Web Developer

MyShoperon, Toronto ON

- Developing responsive web applications across platforms and mobile apps using javascript framework React
- Worked with a team of backend developers to ensure all the frontend designs met the highest level standard of coding
- Worked in an Agile-driven environment to effectively maintain project timelines and utilize available resources.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- Reviewed code to validate structures, assess security and verify browser, device and operating system compatibility.
- Used React, Node, MongoDB, SASS and JSX to develop app-solutions.
- Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.

2020-09 - Current

Front End Developer - Co-op

Toronto Tech Mentoring, Toronto ON

- Developed designs to meet specific requirements such as quick-loading sites with particular layouts.
- Completed full redesigns of existing websites to improve navigation, enhance visuals and strengthen search engine rankings.
- Collaborated with in-house web designers to create sleek and innovative UI design.
- Managed full-cycle design tasks, handling all phases from conception to completion while maintaining guidelines throughout.

Education

2020-01 - 2020-09	Certificate - Full Stack Web Developer University of Toronto - Toronto
2012-01 - 2015-06	Bachelor's Degree- Engineering Technology Manufacturing Cape Breton University - Nova Scotia
2012-01 - 2015-06	Advanced Diploma- Mechanical Engineering Design George Brown College - Toronto